A Guide to Papers of the Virginia Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs 1924-1994
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Virginia Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs 1924-1994
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
11175
There are 4200 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Deposit: Feb 2, 1995 by Nancy Tyler, Goode, Va. 24556.
Scope and Content Information
The collection contains annual reports; annual state and district reports; minutes of the Board of Directors, the Executive Committee, the annual convention, and Federation presidents; and the Federation's journals, particularly Federation Notes and National Business Woman.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by series.
Contents List
- Topical Material
  - Annual Reports 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports 1967-1968 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports 1968-1973 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports 1973-1976 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports 1977-1980 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports 1980-1983 (Box 2)
  - Annual State and District Reports 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Annual State and District Reports 1971-1972 (Box 2)
  - Annual State and District Reports 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Annual State and District Reports 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Annual State and District Reports 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Annual State and District Reports 1975-1977 (Box 4)
  - Annual State and District Reports 1977-1979 (Box 5)
  - Annual State and District Reports 1979-1981 (Box 6)
  - Annual State and District Reports 1981-1983 (Box 6)
  - Minutes of the Executive Committee Meetings, Board of Director Meetings and State Convention 1983 May-Jun (Box 7)
  - Minutes of Program Planning Conference, Executive Committee Meetings, and Board of Directors Meetings 1983 May-Jun (Box 7)
  - Minutes of Board Meeting and Leadership Conference and Executive Committee Meetings 1983 Sep (Box 7)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings 1984 Jan-Mar (Box 7)
  - Minutes of Pre-Convention Executive Committee Meeting 1984 May (Box 7)
  - Minutes of Board of Directors Meeting and State Convention 1984 May (Box 7)
  - Minutes of Board of Directors Meeting 1984 May (Box 8)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings 1984 May-Jun (Box 8)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings 1984 Sep (Box 8)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meeting and Board Meeting 1984 Sep-Oct (Box 8)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings and Board Meeting 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meeting 1985 May (Box 8)
  - Minutes of Board of Directors Meeting 1985 May (Box 8)
  - Minutes of Board Meetings and Executive Committee Meeting 1985 May-Sep (Box 8)
  - Minutes of Fall Board Meeting and Mid-Winter Executive Committee Meeting 1985 Sep-1986 Feb (Box 8)
  - Minutes of Annual Convention and Pre-Convention Meeting 1986 May (Box 9)
  - Minutes of Board Meeting and Executive Committee Meetings 1986 May-Jun (Box 9)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings and Fall Board and Leadership Conference 1986 Sep-1987 Jan (Box 9)
  - Minutes of Annual Connvention and Pre-Convention Meetings 1987 May (Box 9)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetins and Post-Convention Board Meeting 1987 May-Jun (Box 9)
  - Minutes of Fall Board and Leadership Conference and Executive Committee Meetins 1987 Sep (Box 9)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Planning Meeting 1988 Jan (Box 9)
  - Minutes of 67th Annual Convention 1988 May 20-22 (Box 10)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings and Board of Directors Meeting 1988 May (Box 10)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings and Board of Director Meeting 1988 May-Sep (Box 10)
  - Minutes of Fall Board and Leadership Conference and Winter Executive Committee Meeting 1988 Sep-1989 Jan (Box 10)
  - Minutes of State Annual Convention, Pre-convention Board Meeting, and Pre-Convention Executive Committee Meeting 1989 May (Box 10)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings and Board Meeting 1989 May-1990 Jan (Box 10)
  - Minutes of Annual State Convention, Board Meeting, and Executive Committee Meeting 1990 May (Box 10)
  - Minutes compiled by President Gladys B. White 1958-1959 (Box 11)
  - Minutes compiled by President Dorothy V. Allport 1959-1960 (Box 11)
  - Minutes compiled by President Nettie T. Yowell 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Minutes compiled by President Gale B. Hounshell 1961-1963 (Box 11)
  - Minutes compiled by President Nellie F. Garrett 1963-1964 (Box 11)
  - Minutes compiled by President Jane J. Palmer 1964-1965 (Box 11)
  - Minutes compiled by President Agnes M. Ames 1965-1966 (Box 11)
  - Minutes compiled by President Doris E. Kean 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Minutes compiled by President Josephine A. Turrentine 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Minutes compiled by President Prudence O. Tedder 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Minutes compiled by President Vivian W. Giles 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - Minutes compiled by President Theda T. Fitzpatrick 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Minutes compiled by President Buena M. Chesshir 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Minutes compiled by President Karen R. Keesling 1990-1991 (Box 12)
  - Minutes compiled by President Karen L. Lewis 1991-1992 (Box 12)
- Printed Material
  - Federation Notes 1952-1994, 5 folders (Box 13)
  - Let's Go 1925-1935, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Independent Woman 1924-1926 (Box 13)
  - National Business Woman 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - National Business Woman 1970-1978, 8 folders (Box 14)
  - National Business Woman 1979-1994, 7 folders (Box 15)
  - The Virginia Business and Professional Woman 1938-1949 (Box 15)